http://www.catertrax.com/privacy-policy/

No Announcement posts
CaterTrax Privacy Policies
Introduction
When submitting your information to CaterTrax, we understanding you are trusting us. We take that responsibility seriously. This starts with helping you understand our privacy policies.
Please view our privacy policies below. If you have any questions or concerns please contact us at 1-800-975-8729 or support@catertrax.com.
Expand Section to View CaterTrax Policy
CaterTrax Privacy Statement
Download Standard Privacy Policy PDFPRIVACY STATEMENTThis Privacy Policy applies to “You”, as the end user of the CaterTrax website, and exclusively to the information practices of CaterTrax Inc. (“CaterTrax”) related to our website, catertrax.com. Further, if You use our website (catertrax.com, which is the site you’re reading this on at this very moment), then this page is for You. Among other things, it talks about what constitutes a legitimate use of our website. Although this website contains links to other websites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those, or any other sites. If You follow a link to another website you should carefully read their privacy policy. When You use this Site or do business through this Site, You are giving CaterTrax permission to process your Personally Identifiable Information as described below and You accept this Privacy Statement.PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATIONAny Personally Identifiable Information that You submit to our website will only be used to service your account and/or to provide You with information on CaterTrax products and services. The types of Personal Information that may be collected at our website include:• Your full name• Your mailing address• Your email address• Your telephone numberCaterTrax is the sole owner of all information collected on this site. CaterTrax will not rent, sell or share any Personally Identifiable Information about You with third parties for any reason except when required to assist in resolving an issue You raise with us or as required by law.Information collected on this website may be imported into Mailchimp. You can review Mailchimp’s privacy policy here: https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/AGGREGATE INFORMATIONWe generally record certain usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to our website. This information may include the websites that You access immediately before or after your visit to the CaterTrax website, the Internet browser You are using and your IP address. We use this information for internal use to help us provide a better user experience and to determine what kinds of information our users may find useful. We will not disclose any of this non personally identifiable information to a third party. Again, this information does not identify users personally, only their general behavior while using the CaterTrax website.Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive. Each website that you visit can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser preferences allow it. These cookies do not personally identify the user but only act to help us better understand user needs. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYCaterTrax reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason. Please review this policy periodically for changes. A link to the current version of this Privacy Policy can be accessed from the footer of every page on this website. You acknowledge that by accessing this website after we have posted changes to this Privacy Policy, you are agreeing to the terms of the Privacy Policy as modified.CONTACT USIf You have any questions about this privacy policy please contact us at 1.800.975.8729 or visit our Contact Us page to email a question immediately.
EU GDPR Fair Processing Notice
Download EU GDPR Fair Processing Notice PDFEU GDPR FAIR PROCESSING NOTICEThe Personal Data CaterTrax Inc. (“CaterTrax”) collects from a visitor to catertrax.com (“you”) will only be used by CaterTrax to service your account and/or provide you with information on CaterTrax products and services. This EU GDPR Fair Processing Notice supplements the information contained in CaterTrax’s Standard Privacy Statement and applies solely to all visitors, users, and others who reside in the European Union.WHAT IS PERSONAL DATA? Under the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“EU GDPR”): Personal Data is defined as “any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (“Data Subject”); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.”SPECIAL CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATACertain data is classified under the EU GDPR as special categories and for purposes of this statement are referred to as “Sensitive Personal Data”:RacialEthnic originPolitical OpinionsReligious BeliefsTrade-union membershipGenetic DataBiometric DataHealth DataData concerning a natural person’s sex lifeSexual orientationOtherWHY DOES CATERTRAX NEED TO COLLECT AND STORE PERSONAL DATA?In order for CaterTrax to provide adequate follow up regarding doing business or potential business with a client/prospect, we capture minimal information so that we can conduct business. The Personal Data CaterTrax may collect includes:Your full nameYour e-mail addressYour phone number(s)Your mailing addressOther personal or preference information you provide to usIn any event, CaterTrax is committed to ensuring that the information it collects and uses is appropriate for this purpose and does not constitute an invasion of your privacy. CaterTrax may pass your Personal Data on to its third-party service providers who are contracted to CaterTrax (“Contractors”) in the course of dealing with you. Those Contractors are obliged to keep your details secure and use them only to fulfill the service they provide you on our behalf. Once your service need has been satisfied or the case has been closed, they will dispose of the details in accordance with CaterTrax’s procedures.USING YOUR PERSONAL DATACaterTrax will use the information you provide for the following purposes:To contact you regarding an inquiryTo send you company and product-related informationCaterTrax will process – that means collect, store and use – the information you provide in a manner that is compatible with the EU GDPR. CaterTrax will endeavor to keep your information accurate and up to date and not keep it for longer than is necessary. In some instances, the law sets the length of time information must be kept, but in most cases CaterTrax will use its discretion to ensure that it does not keep records outside of our normal business requirements.Our aim is not to be intrusive, and CaterTrax undertakes not to ask irrelevant or unnecessary questions. Moreover, the information you provide will be subject to rigorous measures and procedures to minimize the risk of unauthorized access or disclosure.CONSENT TO PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL DATABy utilizing the CaterTrax system, you are giving CaterTrax permission to perform those actions and to process your Personal Data as described above. You may request access to or deletion of your data here or by calling 800-975-TRAX. As a result of your request, you will be given a form to complete which will provide CaterTrax with your withdrawal consent to process data per the EU GDPR. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Data if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the Personal Data relates to you. We will only use Personal Data provided in a verifiable request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request.We endeavor to respond to a verifiable request within thirty (30) days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to 60 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICEWe reserve the right to amend this privacy notice at our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to this privacy notice, we will post the updated notice on the Website and update the notice’s effective date. Your continued use of our Website following the posting of changes constitutes your acceptance of such changes.
California Consumer Privacy Act
Download California Consumer Privacy Notice PDFCALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY NOTICEAs a California resident, this Privacy Notice applies exclusively to the information practices related to our website, catertrax.com. The Personal Information CaterTrax Inc. (“CaterTrax”) collects from a visitor to catertrax.com (“consumers” or “you”) will only be used by CaterTrax to service your account and/or provide you with information on CaterTrax products and services. This California Consumer Privacy Notice supplements the information contained in CaterTrax’s Standard Privacy Statement and applies solely to all visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of California.WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATIONUnder the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”), Personal Information means “information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household.” This includes, among other information, your name, email, payment card information, identification number, and certain data received from tracking technologies. Personal Information does not include Publicly available information from government records and Deidentified or Aggregate consumer information.WHY DOES CATERTRAX NEED TO COLLECT AND STORE PERSONAL INFORMATIONIn order for CaterTrax to provide adequate follow up regarding doing business or potential business with a client/prospect, we capture minimal information so that we can conduct business.In particular, we have collected the following categories of Personal Information from its consumers within the last twelve (12) months:Category A: IdentifiersCategory B: Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))Category F: Internet or other similar network activityThe Personal Information CaterTrax may collect includes:Your full nameYour e-mail addressYour phone number(s)Your mailing addressOther personal or preference information You provide to usHOW CATERTRAX USES YOUR INFORMATIONCaterTrax will use the information You provide for the following purposes:To contact you regarding your inquiryTo send you company and product-related informationCaterTrax will process – that means collect, store, and use – the information You provide in a manner that is compatible with the CCPA. We will not collect additional categories of Personal Information or use the Personal Information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice. CaterTrax will endeavor to keep your information accurate and up to date and not keep it for longer than is necessary. In some instances, the law sets the length of time information must be kept, but in most cases CaterTrax will use its discretion to ensure that it does not keep records outside of our normal business requirements. The information You provide will be subject to rigorous measures and procedures to minimize the risk of unauthorized access or disclosure.HOW CATERTRAX SHARES YOUR INFORMATIONWe may disclose your Personal Information to a third party for a business purpose. When we disclose Personal Information for a business purpose, we enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that Personal Information confidential and not use it for any purpose except performing the contract.We share your Personal Information with the following categories of third parties:Service providers.Disclosures of Personal Information for a Business PurposeIn the preceding twelve (12) months, Company has disclosed the following categories of Personal Information for a business purpose:Category A: IdentifiersCategory B: Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))Category F: Internet or other similar network activityWe disclose your Personal Information for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties:Service providers, including the providers necessary to host the CaterTrax website.SALE OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONCaterTrax does not sell or rent your Personal Information.CONSENT TO PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL DATABy utilizing the CaterTrax website, you are giving CaterTrax permission to perform those actions and to process your Personal Information as described above.You may request access to or deletion of your data here or by calling 800-975-TRAX. As a result of your request, you will be given a form to complete which will provide CaterTrax with your withdrawal consent to process data per the CCPA. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the Personal Information relates to you. We will only use Personal Information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request.We endeavor to respond to a verifiable consumer request within forty-five (45) days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to 45 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.NON-DISCRIMINATIONWe will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:Deny you goods or services.Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to amend this privacy notice at our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to this privacy notice, we will post the updated notice on the Website and update the notice’s effective date. Your continued use of our Website following the posting of changes constitutes your acceptance of such changes.
Information Request
If you would like to place a request regarding your information as outlined in one of these policies please complete the form below and a CaterTrax representative will assist you.
Policy Type*EU GDPRCCPAName*
First
Last
Company*Title*Email*
PhoneRequest Type*Right of AccessRight of ErasureData PortabilityRequest Type*Right to KnowRight to DeleteMore InformationCommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Copyright © , CaterTrax, Inc. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy
